ADENUGA SAMIAT ADEPEJU

7 Adefisan Close, behind drovans hotel ring road Ibadan Oyo State.

E-mail address:samiattella@yahoo.com
Contact No: 08030414730. Date of Birth: 12thApril1989

CAREER SUMMARY:

A highly resourceful, flexible, reliable, and focused individual who possess a considerable amount of knowledge regarding administrative and office procedures. A quick learner who can absorb new ideas and is experienced in coordinating, planning and organizing a wide range of administrative activities.

Well organized and an excellent team player with a proven ability to work proactively in a complex and busy office environment.

SKILLS:

- Active Learning
- Ability to work under pressure with high level of accuracy.
- Administration and control
- Proficient with the use of Microsoft Office Packages
- Good communication skill
- Procurement
- Supply Management

EXPERIENCE:

CASHIER/SALES EXECUTIVE from 11/2018 till date **COMPOVINE TECHNOLOGIES LIMITED-**Ibadan

- Welcome and address customers in a professional manner.
- Manage a high volume of customers in courteous and friendly way.
- Inform customers about available products, ongoing sales, discounts and promotions.
- Give product suggestions to customers when needed.
- Assist customers in product selections based on their needs.
- Perform cash or credit card transactions for customer purchases.
- Handle cash register and manage cash receivable and payables.
- Arrange the product display areas in a visually appealing manner.
- Assist in keeping the store and stock area clean and orderly.

- Collaborate with sales team to offer quality customer services.
- Execute operational and sale techniques while extending outstanding services to customers.

FINANCE AND ADMINISTRATIVE COORDINATOR from 05/2015 to 09/2018

MADAMSABI MARKET SERVICES- Yaba.

- Collect and deposit money into account, disburse funds from cash accounts to pay bills or invoices, keep records of collection, disbursement and ensure accounts are balanced.
- Create, maintain and enter information on databases.
- Setup and manage paper or electronic filing systems, recording information, updating paperwork's and maintaining document such as attendance records, correspondence or other material.
- Provide services to customers such as procurement, order placement or account information.
- Direct the maintenance of general subsidiary ledger, petty cash, account receivables, operating expenses and reconciliation of records.
- Responsible for balancing inventory entry and exit manual entry on the system.

ACCOUNTING TRAINEE from 09/2013 to 04/2015. **G.O GBEDE AUDIT PROFESSIONAL** - Sabo Yaba Lagos.

- Operate office equipment such as computers, copier, and scanner and arrange for repair when equipment malfunctions.
- Preparation of financial reports, review of reconciliation, preparation of financial and management account for client and organization.
- Partake in Field Audit, checking out for expenses procured and evaluating the profit and loss account of the organization.

ACCOUNT ASSISTANT AND CASHIER from 11/2010 to 10/2011(NYSC) CFAO GENERAL IMPORT& DISTRIBUTION LIMITED - Maiduguri

- Preparation of the company's broad sheets, issuing of receipts to customers, also relating with customers on how goods can be purchased from the company and get delivery.
- Collect and deposit money into account, disburse cash and also ensure all necessary accounts are balanced.

EDUCATION:

Masters of Education: Educational Administration and planning *from 2014 to 2016*

University of Lagos Akoka Lagos Nigeria.

Information Technology (certificate) University of Lagos Akoka. (2012) **Bachelor of Science in Education B.sc(Ed):** Accounting from 2006 to 2010

Grade Level: Second class upper division

Tai Solanrin University of Education Ijagunljebu-ode Ogun State.

Secondary School Leaving Certificate from 2003 to 2005. **Tunyo Comprehensive College Igando Egan.**

Primary School Leaving Certificate, from 1999 to 2002. Tunyo Nursery and Primary School Papa Ajao Mushin Lagos.

HOBBIES:

Meeting People, Studying, Crafting, and Cooking.

REFEREES:

Mrs. M.O Sanni CFAO General Import & Distribution Lagos. 08033050967.

MrTaofikAgbabiaka

Federal Inland Revenue Maryland Lagos. 08035729308

MrGbengaAsipa

CFAO General Import & Distribution 08051051761, 08098855061